The Edinburgh,
a city-state with profound historical and cultural heritage. As the capital of Scotland,
Edinburgh,
has been a centre of art and culture since medieval times.
Over the years,
it has created the unique cultural scenes of Edinburgh,
public art and cultural stories.
that can be seen everywhere.
Our challenge: cultural Map of Edinburgh provide us with detailed information on public art resources in Edinburgh.
After proper analysis of the data,
we tried to use digital and physical techniques to show people this number and the scale of public art in Edinburgh.
within long tradition of the public art,
So there is our interactive device Edinburgh
Art time.
Our installation contains physical maps and interactive screens.
When visitors wants to learn more about the public art in Edinburgh,
they find our map and saw how the public art is distributed in Edinburgh. To find more detailed information of City Center,
which have the most public art.
They can touch the columns on the physical model,
the websites shown the screen unfold.
the information of specific marks in public art.
The Web page gives visitors instructions on how to use the installation, displays specific information about the art they clicked on.
And if visitors are interested,
they can view relevant data about the overall art of Edinburgh.
Our audience is visitors to Edinburgh and will hope to increase their interest and encouraged them to further explore the public part of this city.